I need to be rooted. I need to not be running around. I need to be in one spot where people
can find me, whether they're good or bad people. Also, just for myself, I love that I'll get
to be in the hood. This was my literal hood that I was in for the past 12 years before
I moved, trying to figure out my way, trying to find my way. Like, that was where I was
on the hill. So when I even pulled up to Jamie's spot, it was like serendipitous because
it was like, hold up, this was my train stop. Then come to find out Jamie's father is from
Grenada. So it's like, I keep being called home and I realize like you need to hear and
listen to what you keep being called home. So then that's where I need to be. Then I keep
being called back to spaces I was in to make new decisions that create more growth. So
I'm being called back to Harlem. I'm being called back to the name Amanda Diva. I'm being called
back to music, all to be in fertile ground and grow something more sustainable for those
who, who want to be engaged with that. And, you know, that's what I feel is my call.
And I think a lot of people want to hold me to perceptions or experiences or things that
have taken place in the past, but a lot of us don't grow, but I do.